看来因特网是不会消失了
So it seems like this lnternet thing is here to stay,huh?
不说话也没关系
It's okay not to talk.
你们猜怎样？ 贝瑞和明蒂要离婚了
Hey,you guys,guess what.Barry and Mindy are getting a divorce.
天哪
-Oh,my God.
你是怎么搞的？
What is the matter with you?
不，是贝瑞和明蒂
No. Barry and Mindy.
对不起 我一听到离婚就觉得是罗斯
Oh,sorry. I hear "divorce," I immediately go to Ross.
谁是贝瑞和明蒂？
Who's Barry and Mindy?
贝瑞是我差点要嫁的人 明蒂是我最要好的朋友
Barry was the guy that I almost married,and Mindy was my best friend.
他们不是有一腿吗？
Wasn't he cheating on you with her?
对，但那只表示他做到一半 会在她身上睡着
But that just means he was falling asleep on top of her instead of me.
他们为什么要离婚？
-Why did they get divorced?
显然是他外遇被她逮到
-Well,apparently...she caught him cheating on her with someone else.
很悲哀吧？
Isn't that sad?
要是我真的嫁给他 我的人生会多么不同
Can you imagine if I'd married him? How different would my life be?
我懂你的意思，我总是在想 要是我没有离婚会怎样
I've always wondered how different my life would be...if I'd never gotten divorced.
哪一次？ 第一次啦
-Which time? -The first time!
真的，要是卡萝没发现 她是同性恋
Imagine if Carol hadn't realized she was a lesbian.
我无法想像 我老是往好的方面去想
I can't. I keep seeing it the good way.
那我一定还在练控手道 （空手道）
I bet I'd still be doing my karate.
后来我经常练控手道
Towards the end of our marriage,I did a lot of karate to release the tension...
好发泄缺乏肉体运动的精力
from not doing anything else physical.
也许你不念成控手道就没事了
Maybe the problem was you were pronouncing it "ka-ra-tay."
如果我还是很胖呢？
What if I was still fat?
你一定不会跟我交往
You wouldn't be dating me,that's for sure.
当然会 少来了
-Sure I would. -Come on.
你们真的觉得我那么肤浅？
You guys really think I'm that shallow?
不，我只是觉得莫妮卡太胖
No,I just think Monica was that fat.
要是我没被 “我们的日子”开除呢？
Hey,imagine if I'd never got fired off Days of Our Lives.
卡萝又出现了
Hey. Hey,there's Carol again.
要是我有勇气辞职呢？
What if I had had the guts to quit my job?
我可能在帮“纽约客”（美国第一位的文学杂志）写稿 拿钱搞笑
I'd probably be writing for The New Yorker,being paid to be funny.
现在的工作也很有趣 明天我不必打领带
But my job's fun too. I mean,tomorrow...I don't have to wear a tie.
要是我去美林证券上班呢？
What if I'd taken that job at Merrill Lynch?
什么？ 美林证券？
-What? -Merrill Lynch?
对，我有个客人在那里上班
I had a massage client who worked there,
他说我有炒股票的头脑
and he said I had a knack for stocks.
那你怎么不去？
Why didn't you take the job?
因为当时我很相信押韵这回事
Because at that time,I thought that everything that rhymed was true.
我觉得要是我去做股票 就得住地窖
I thought if I worked with stocks...I'd have to live in a box
只能吃安眠药，养三脚猫
and only eat lox and have a pet fox.
这种股票经纪人的确不是你想要的
Yeah,you don't want that in a broker.
你们觉得如果有这些事 我们还会在一起吗？
Do you guys think if all those things happened,we'd still hang out?
本集播出：“可能会发生的事”
The One That Could Have Been
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯阿奎特
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
天哪，瑞秋格林？
Oh,my God. Rachel Green?
劳勃提尔曼
Rob Tilman!
不对，是我，罗斯
No,no,it's me. Ross.
对不起，罗斯提尔曼
Oh,I'm sorry. Ross Tilman.
不是，是罗斯盖勒
-No. No,no. Ross Geller.
当然了，莫妮卡的哥哥
Of course! Monica's brother.
没错
-Yeah. Right.
你好吗？ 很好，我结婚了
-Wow! How are you?Good. Good. I'm married.
我也是
Me too!
结婚真好不是吗？ 就是啊
-Isn't it the best? -Oh,it's the best.
莫妮卡好吗？ 非常好
-So how's Monica? -Really,really great.
事实上她就在前面
Actually,she's right down the street.
你应该过去打个招呼
You should stop by and say hi.
好啊 她会很高兴
-I would love to. -She'd be so excited.
好 走吧
-Okay. -Come on.
等等，你不是要买…
Wait,don't you have to pay for...
“巨乳女O”？
Busty Ladies?
没关系，有个小孩托我帮他买
No,that's okay. Some kid asked me to pick it up for him,but I....
走吧
Okey
你不是应该把钱还给他？
Don't you have to give him his money back?
拿去吧，抱歉，你不能看色情书
Here you go,buddy. Sorry,no porn for you.
我们去找莫妮卡吧
Okay,let's go see Monica.
莫妮卡 你还在跟无聊医生交往？
So,Monica. Still going out with Dr. Boring,huh?
他才不无聊，他只是…
He's not boring. He's just...
只是比较低调
He's low-key.
你的榛果拿铁 谢谢
-Here you go,one hazelnut latte. -Thank you.
其实榛果不是果实，而是种子
You know,the hazelnut,actually not a nut.It's a seed.
还有谁能说出一种 假装是果实的常见种子？
Can anyone else name a well-known seed that's been masquerading as a nut?
天哪，我想想看
Oh,dear God. Let me think.
你怎么了？ 我又被退稿了
What's the matter?I got another rejection letter.
他们说我的东西很有趣 只是不如“阿奇漫画”有趣
They said my writing was funny,just not "Archie Comic" funny.
亲爱的，我得回医院了 好
I gotta get back to the hospital.
再见
-Bye. -Bye-bye.
对了，答案是巴西坚果
By the way,the answer is: the Brazil nut.
他的问题比他的人更无趣
Was his question,"What's more boring than him?"
好帅的毛线背心啊
And nice sweater vest,by the way.
你们别这样，他人很好 是啊
-Stop it,guys. He's sweet. -Yeah,yeah.
老兄，退稿的事真可惜 你要我借给你一些钱吗？
Hey,man. Sorry about the Archie thing.You need me to give you some money?
我穷归穷，还是有骨气
I may have no money,but I still have my pride.
是吗？
Really?
也许乔伊不必给你钱 电视明星都有助理对吧？
Joey doesn't have to give you the money.TV stars have assistants,right?
这个办法好
That's an idea.
要是我请助理转交 你会收吗？
If I hire an assistant,would you take money from her?
不是啦，钱德可以当你的助理
No,Joey. Chandler could be your assistant.
他可以帮你回信给影迷
He could answer all your fan mail and stuff.
太好了，好主意，就这么办吧
-That would be great! Let's do that! -I could use the money.
我有钱领，还有时间写作
I'd have time to write.
漂亮，欢迎加入 感谢
-Great. Welcome aboard! -Okay!
我现在要去上厕所 我上厕所不用人帮
All right. Now,I need to use the bathroom.Since I don't need any assistance in there,
你就休息吧 好
take a break!All right.
菲比，你猜怎样？ 怎样？
-Hey. -Hey,Phoebe.Guess what.
乔伊找钱德当他的助理
Joey just hired Chandler to be his assistant.
真好
That's so sweet.
等一下，等我一下
Oh! Hang on!Hang on!
说
Go!
不对，不对 我是说一到50点就卖
No. No,no. I said sell when it hits 50!
50是一个数字，在49后面
Five-oh! It's a number! It comes after four-nine!
没关系，一次错误可以接受
No,it's okay. It's okay. You're allowed one mistake.
开玩笑的，你当然被开除了
Just kidding. You are,of course,fired.
真可惜，我很喜欢她
Oh,what a shame. I really liked her.
莫妮卡，你看我遇见谁
Hey,Mon? Mon,look who I ran into!
天哪，瑞秋
Oh,my God,Rachel!
你看起来太不可思议了 你也是
-God,you look terrific! -So do you!
你是不是瘦了？
-Did you lose weight?
你居然注意到了 没错，我瘦了3.5磅
-You are so sweet to notice.Yes,I lost 3.5 pounds!
记得我的朋友钱德吧
You remember my friend Chandler.
那位是菲比
-And that's Phoebe over there. -Hi.
天哪，快坐下
Sit down.
我们多久没见面了？
How long has it been since we've seen each other?
1987年，圣诞节第二天 西恩麦克曼的派对
1987,the day after Christmas. Sean McMahan's party.
我弹了我的创作曲给你听 “星际求爱仪式”
I played you one of my songs,you know,"lnterplanetary Courtship Ritual."
喔对
Oh,yeah. Right.
你还在玩音乐吗？
-So,now,do you still do music?
偶尔，你应该来我家，我弹…
-Well,sometimes.Come over sometime. I'll play you..
天哪，“我们的日子”的 乔伊崔比亚尼刚刚走进来
-Oh,my God!Joey Tribbiani from Days of Our Lives just walked in here!
瑞秋，他是我们的朋友
-Rach,he's a friend of ours.
你们是雷莫瑞医生的朋友？
-You're friends with Dr. Drake Ramoray?
要跟他交朋友有点难 因为他很忙，又是个虚构人物
It's hard to be friends with Drake...because of his busy schedule and the fact that he's not real.
我也可以把键盘带来
Hey,or I could bring my keyboard here sometime.
他过来了
-He's coming over. -Joey?
乔伊 好啦，拿去
I know. Here,here.
不是啦，这是我朋友瑞秋 我们是高中同学
No. This is my friend Rachel. We went to high school together.
我好喜欢你演的戏 我每天都看
I love you on that show.I watch you every day.
你的前妻明明想杀你 你还捐肾救她…
When you took out your own kidney to save your ex-wife...even though she tried to kill you
遇见影迷总是很开心
It's always nice to meet fans.
她不会很神经吧？ 不会
-She's not crazy,is she? -No.
所以…你好吗？
So how you doing?
等等…等等，等一下
Hang on.Hang on. Hang on.
说
Go!
谁？
Who's this?
好，你要替我工作 你叫什么名字？
You're gonna like working for me.What's your name?
布伦蒂是什么鸟名字？
What kind of name is "Brindy"?
我…随便…闭嘴
I…Whatever…Stop talking.
好，以后你就叫琼安
All right,from now on your name is Joan.
姓你自己选
You can pick your own last name.
我找不到我的笔 也被你吃掉了吗？
I can't find my pen. Did you eat that too?
你在这里 是老板大人
-There you are. -Uh-oh,it's my boss.
这是你今天的工作项目
Here's a list of things for you to do today.
太好了，谢谢你
This is gonna be so great. Thank you so much.
我要去给双胞胎接生了 但只有一个是我的骨肉
I gotta go to work. I'm delivering twins today,but only one of them is mine.
把衣服送去干洗 去拿我的维他命
"Drop off my dry cleaning. Pick up my vitamins."
教我怎么写维他命
"Teach me how to spell vitamins."
把我的新牛仔裤穿软
"Wear in my new jeans."
你知道你的角色吧？
-You realize what you are,don't you? -What?
什么角色？ 你像他的婆娘
You're his bitch!
不！不
No,no! No!
你不是压坏了我的巧克力酥吧
Wait! You didn't sit on my Kit Kats did you?
不是，市场出了点变化
No,there was a little,little dip in the market...
我损失了1千3百万
and I lost 13 million dollars.
不过巧克力酥没事吧？
But the Kit Kats are all right?
怎么办？怎么办？ 通知公司我会被砍死
What am I gonna do? I can't call my office,they'll kill me.
通知客户他们会砍自己
I can't call my clients,they'll kill themselves!
好啊，现在又胸口痛
-Great,now my chest hurts.
什么？ 我的胸口在痛
-What?My chest hurts.
现在是喘不过气来
-And now I can't breathe.
菲比，你是心脏病发作吗？
-Are you having a heart attack?
如果是，左臂会来回抽痛吗？
If I were,would I have shooting pains up and down my left arm?
会 那就是了
-Yes. -Then,yes. That is what I'm having.
我的天哪
Oh,my God!
我的手动不了了 帮我拨911好吗？
Okay,this thing is useless. So will you dial 911 for me?
别这样，没那么严重
Come on,Phoebe,it's not that bad.
一般人如果可以休息两星期 会很兴奋的
Most people would be excited if they didn't work for a couple weeks.
一般人不喜欢他们的工作 我喜欢我的工作
Most people don't like their jobs. I love my job.
我才休息3小时就快疯掉了
I've been not working for three hours,and I'm already going crazy.
我想念琼安
I miss Joan.
心脏病发就表示你该放慢脚步
Honey,having a heart attack is nature's way of telling you to slow down.
我一直以为心脏病发 就表示你要死了
I always thought having a heart attack was nature's way of telling you to die.
但是你不会死
You're not gonna die.
你迟早会死，但不是今天
I mean,you are going to die,but you're not gonna die today.
我去死算了
I wish I was dead.
我们去走走
Let's take a walk.
你应该考虑去替 “用屁股讲话”杂志写稿
You should consider writing for Talking Out of Your Ass magazine.
你最近怎么样？
What's going on with you?
我练控手道练得更勤了
Well,I've been doing a lot more of my karate.
跟卡萝还在干枯期？ 对
-Still a dry spell with Carol? -Yeah.
你们多久没上床了？
How long has it been since you've had sex?
上个周末… 那还好嘛
-Well,last weekend... -Oh,that's not so bad.
就已经2个月…放弃尝试了
will be two months...since I stopped trying.
也许你应该玩一点刺激的 怎么说？
You need to spice things up.-What do you mean?
不晓得，你们可以绑住对方 可以在对方身上吃东西
-I don't know.You could tie her up. You could eat stuff off each other.
淫言秽语，辅助工具
Dirty talk,menage a trois,toys.
角色扮演 你当典狱长她当囚犯
Role-playing. You're the warden,she's the prisoner.
你当海盗她当村姑
-You're the pirate,she's the wench.
好，我懂了
-Okay,I think I got it.
或者你们都当股票经纪人 裸身在众人面前滚来滚去
Or you could be two stockbrokers,and you're rolling naked on the trading floor...and everybody's watching.
我没干过
It never happened.
抱歉
Sorry.
你帮乔伊工作得怎样？
-So how is it going with Joey?
很好，他现在都用暗号呼叫我
-Just great. He beeps me now with codes.
1是“带吃的来”
One is: "Bring me food."
2是“有女伴，带吃的来”
Two is: "I'm with a girl. Bring us food."
3是“迷路，找不到吃的”
Three is: "I'm lost and I can't find food."
辛苦你了
Oh,sweetie.
这附近有吃的吗？
Is there any food around here?
她不会有事吧？ 对，她在里面
-Is she gonna be all right? -Yeah,she's in there.
那就好
Oh,great.
可以还我裤子了，看起来够软了
Go take off those pants. They look ready.
那里是布瑞帝酒吧 我做完手术喜欢去轻松一下
And over there is Brady's Pub...where I like to unwind after a long day of "surgeoning."
好棒喔，还有呢？
This is so amazing. What else?
那是一个大型电视台设备
Well,that is a large piece of television equipment.
那是一个老男人，老男人你好
And that is an old man.-Hey,old man! -Hey.
我们要不要回我家去？
Alrighty. What do you say we head back to my place?
我很想去，但是不行
You know,I would really love to,but I shouldn't.
为什么？ 为什么世界不能停止转动
Why? Why can't the world stop turning...
只要一下下，只为了我们？
just for a moment,just for us?
那不是戏里的台词吗？
Isn't that a line from the show?
对，不过
Yeah,but...
我或许说过同样的话，但是…
I may have said those things before,but...
只有这一刻…
I never truly meant them
我才是真心的
until now.
那也是戏里的台词
That's a line from the show too!
你看太多电视了
Okay,you watch too much TV.
乔伊，现榨的柳橙汁来了 谢谢
Here's the freshly squeezed orange juice you asked for.Thanks.
里面有果肉
There's pulp in that.
怎样？
Ya？
我们不是讲过了
I thought we talked about this.
我不喜欢果肉，不要果肉 果肉不是果汁，我要纯果汁
I don't like pulp.No pulp. Pulp isn't juice. All juice.
对不起，我就是喜欢果肉
I'm sorry. I guess I just like the pulp.
天哪，抱歉，我太不客气了
I'm sorry. I am being so rude.
瑞秋，你要喝汽水什么的吗？
Rachel,would you like a soda or something?
钱德会马上去帮你买
Because Chandler will run right out and get it.
好啊，就冰红茶吧
Yeah,well,sure,iced tea would be great.
冰红茶
Iced tea.
好，那您要什么，先生？
Okay. Anything for you,sir?
我刚才不是说了吗？
Did I not just tell him?
钱德，你想替我工作
Okay,look,Chandler,if this is gonna work...
就要专心听我说话
you have got to listen.
你要拿果汁泼我对不对？
You're gonna throw that juice at me,aren't you?
这不是纯果汁
It's not all juice.
亲爱的，早上我在淋浴间扑向你 很有意思吧？
So,honey,this morning was fun,huh?Me hopping in on you in the shower there?
是啊，也许以后可以换一栋 有两间浴室的房子
Yeah,maybe someday we could get a place with two bathrooms.
卡萝，我在想 或许我们可以玩一点刺激的
Look,Carol,I was thinking maybe...Maybe we can spice things up a little.
怎么说？
-What do you mean?
卡萝，我们的性生活不美…
-Carol,our sex life. It's just not..
爸 小鬼头
-Dad! -Hey there,little fella!
你要不要去穿鞋？
Why don't we get some shoes on you,huh?
自己去房里穿鞋给爸爸看
Why don't you show Dad how you can put your shoes on in your room.
说真的，我们的性生活…
Seriously,our sex life.
我想说或许… 我们可以换个新花样玩玩
I was thinking maybe,I don't know...we could try some new things,you know,for fun.
像什么？ 我不知道
-Like what? -Well,I don't know.
互相把对方绑起来如何？
What if we were to...tie each other up?
有些人会在对方身上吃东西
Some people eat stuff off one another.
不好
Yeah.
我们可以说脏话助长情趣
You know,we could try dirty talk.
我们可以玩3P
-We could have a threesome.
这个我喜欢
-I love that idea!
谁的故事被“阿奇漫画”采用了？
Who sold a story to Archie Comics?
天哪，太棒了
Oh,my God,that's so great.
你有著作了，真想送你贺礼
You're a published writer. I wish I had a present for you.
等等
Wait a minute.
我的最后一个巧克力酥
My last Kit Kat bar.
要不要跟我分？ 好啊
-You want to share it? -Okay!
钱德，我知道你很生气 我想跟你道歉
Chandler,I know you're mad. I'm sorry.
我太混蛋、太过了
I was a total jerk. Completely over the line.
但我就是讨厌果肉
I just... I hate pulp.
就像莫妮卡 对低脂美乃滋的感觉
You know how Monica feels about low-fat mayonnaise?
那不是美乃滋
It's not mayonnaise!
总之我只想说对不起 这个给你
Anyway,I just wanted to say I'm sorry,and here.
什么东西？
-What's this?
现榨的柳橙汁 有你喜欢的果肉
-Fresh-squeezed orange juice,with pulp.Just the way you like it.
谢了
Thanks,man.
乔伊
Hey,Joey.
乔伊，钱德的故事 被“阿奇漫画”采用了
Joey? Chandler sold a story to Archie Comics.
天哪，太棒了，恭喜
That's great! Congratulations!
是什么故事？
What's the story?
也没什么 只是个白痴的漫画故事
You wouldn't care. It's just a stupid comic book story.
开什么玩笑 我最爱阿奇那票人了
Are you kidding me? I love Archie and the whole gang.
阿奇需要钱修他的老爷车
Well,Archie needs money to fix his jalopy.
但他不想跟瑞吉（阿奇漫画中有钱人）拿钱
But he doesn't want Reggie to just give him the money.
所以瑞吉就找他当助…
So Reggie hires him as his assist..
当管家
As his butler.
然后叫他做一堆无聊事 例如叫他买不能有结块的奶昔
And then makes him do crazy things...Like bring him milk shakes that can't have lumps in them.
等等，有点耳熟喔
Wait a minute. That sounds a little familiar.
这个故事画过了吧 我觉得我看过
Did they already do that one? I think I read it!
莫妮卡，我一定要问
Monica,listen. I have to ask.
乔伊崔比亚尼找我去他家
Okay,Joey Tribbiani invited me back to his apartment.
他经常找女人去他家吗？
-Does he do this with a lot of girls?
对，经常，经常的经常
-Yeah,a lot. A lot,a lot.
而我是其中之一
And I'm one of them.
我真不敢相信 乔伊崔比亚尼耶
I just cannot believe this. I mean,Joey Tribbiani.
你不必一直叫他的姓
You don't have to use his last name.
但是他是乔伊崔比亚尼
But,Monica,come on,it's Joey Tribbiani.
看来你是非叫不可
I guess you have to.
虽然与我无关 但你不是结婚了？
It's none of my business,but aren't you married?
对啊
Yeah.
真希望我们能不结婚一下
I wish we could just not be married for a little bit.
真希望我们能分开一下
You know,I just wish we could be,like,on a break.
你们没有
Well,you're not.
你当然轻松，你又没结婚 爱跟谁上床就跟谁上床
It's easy for you. You're not married. You can have sex with whoever you want.
没错
Yeah,I can.
别以为我没有 我一天到晚都有
Don't think I don't. I do.I mean,all the time. You bet!
莫妮卡
Monica?
你有经验了吧？
You've done it,right?
当然有 你以为我是30岁的老处女吗
Of course I have. What do you think,I'm,like,some 30-year-old virgin?
天哪，你是30岁的老处女
Oh,my God. You're a 30-year-old virgin.
再大声一点 后面那个人应该没听到
Say it louder. The guy in the back didn't hear you.
我听到了
Yeah,I heard it.
我不是没有机会 我只是在等完美的对象
It's not like I haven't had the opportunity.I'm just waiting for the perfect guy.
我正在跟罗杰交往
I'm seeing this guy Roger.
他并不完美，但是…
He's not perfect...but
或许我应该将就一下 把我的花芯给他
I'm thinking maybe I should get it over with.You know,give him my flower.
天哪，那就给吧
Oh,my God,do it!
你等得够久了
Honey,you've waited long enough.
你知道吗？你说得对
-You know what? You are right.
没错，没必要看得那么严重
-Sex doesn't have to be a big deal.
性爱不该有任何规则和限制
There shouldn't be all these rules and restrictions.
人应该随时随地，想跟谁上…
People should be able to sleep with whoever they want,whenever..
瑞秋，我觉得你不该背叛老公
Rachel,I'm never gonna think it's okay for you to cheat on your husband.
你懂什么，处女
What do you know,virgin?
菲比，厕所怎么有烟冒出来？
Phoebe?Why is smoke coming out of the bathroom?
医生说可能会有这种副作用
The doctor said that could be one of the side effects.
菲比，把烟熄掉
Put the cigarette out.
不，那不是香烟 烟是从我身上冒出来的
No,it's not a cigarette. The smoke is coming out of me!
熄掉 好啦好啦
-Put it out. -Okay,okay!
真高兴有你们在
-I'm so glad you're here.
躺好
-Come on.
我来接 给我
-I got it. -Give it to me!
-I got it. -Give it!
喂？
Hello?
她现在不方便接电话
She can't come to the phone now.
好，没问题，再见
Right. No problem. Okay,bye-bye.
是公司吗？他们生气吗？ 是杰克吗？他有发火吗？
Was it my work? Were they mad? Was it Jack? Did he yell?
别紧张，没有人发火
No,just relax. Nobody yelled.
杰克只是打来问你有没有好转
Jack was making sure you were getting better.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
她被开除了
Yeah,she's fired.
你已经尽力了，卫斯理医生，该放手了
You've done all you can,Dr. Wesley.You've got to let her go.
别了，好好安息吧
Goodbye and Godspeed,Hope Brady.
且慢，卫斯理
Not so fast,Wesley.
雷莫瑞
Ramoray!
没错，卫斯理，我只是来说
That's right,Wesley.I just stopped by to say that
你是个冒牌医生
you're not a real doctor.
那个女人的脑部好得很
And that woman's brain is fine.
太好了
Oh,thank God.
霍普，霍普
-Hope? Hope?
德瑞克
-Drake..
霍普，你不会死
You're not dying,Hope
你会跟我过着幸福快乐的日子   哦，德瑞克
You're gonna live a long,healthy life. With me.Oh,Drake.
好，我决定了
Okay.Here we go.
乔伊，我是瑞秋
Hi,Joey? It's Rachel.
我明天晚上有空
I am free tomorrow night.
没问题，我可以带三明治去
Yeah,sure,sure,I can bring some sandwiches.
亲爱的，关于玩3P的事
So,honey...this threesome thing?
你要去哪里找…
How are we even gonna start to find..?
我把可能有兴趣的女人 列了出来
Actually,I'm making a list of women I know who might be into this.
天哪
Boy.
有人很用功喔
Someone's been doing their homework.
是啊 我知道我列了两次盖儿罗斯坦
I know Gail Rosten is in there twice...
是因为她… 我知道
but she is so....Oh,I know.
光是用讲的就让我有点…
You know,just talking about it is getting me kind of...
我也是
I know. Me too.
是吗？班已经睡了
I think Ben's asleep.
我觉得我们最好储存精力
You know,I think it'll be better if we just save it.
储存精力，没问题
Right. Save it. I can do that.
你为什么老是戴着那顶帽子？ 送报要迟到了吗？
Why do you always wear that dumb hat?What,you late for your paper route?
“琼斯先生太太，报纸来了”
"Hi,Mr. and Mrs. Jones. Here's your paper.
“抱歉砸破你们的窗户”
I'm sorry about your window."
菲比
Hey,Phoebe.
还好吗？ 我得离开这张床，我快疯掉了
How's it going?I've got to get out of this bed. I'm going crazy here! Crazy!
喝吧
Here you go,sweetie.
这是花草茶？我讨厌花草茶
What the hell is this,herbal tea? I hate herbal tea.
但是我加了蜂蜜
Well,I put some honey in it.
她还不知道她被开除了对吧？
-She doesn't know she was fired?
对，医生说她知道的话会没命的
-No,the doctors say it may kill her.
你们两个女生在窃窃私语什么
What are you girls whispering about over there?
不过我觉得应该告诉她
But I think we should tell her.
菲比，也许心脏病发是个征兆
Look,Phoebe,maybe this whole heart-attack thing is a sign...
提醒你该考虑转行了
that you should start thinking about getting a different job.
现在是在比赛谁笨吗？
Okay,what is this,a stupid contest?
优胜者已经揭晓了
Because we've got a winner here.
菲比，他说得对 31岁不应该有心脏病
He's right. People are not supposed to have heart attacks at 31.
我知道，但是不做股票 我还能做什么？
I know. But if I didn't work there,what else would I do?
你以前喜欢弹吉他
-You used to like playing the guitar.
真有吸引力啊 跟你哥一样聪明
-That was lucrative. Smart like your brother.
那按摩呢？ 按摩可没让你生过病
What about the massage thing? That never gave you a heart attack.
拿六位数的薪水 帮恶心的裸男裸女按摩赚小钱
Pulling in a salary in the high six figures...or rubbing gross naked people for chump change.
我该怎么选择？
What do I do? What will I do?
它好逼真喔 就是啊
I mean,it's just so realistic.I know.
他的名字叫拍拍 拍拍狗
His name's Pat.Pat the dog.
我懂了
I get it!
你…要续杯了吗？
Ready for a refill?
我不该再喝了…我要喝
I probably shouldn't.So I will!
感觉好像下雨喔 很酷吧？
-It's like it's raining. -Pretty cool,huh?
要是你以为把鱼扔进去 不会卡进机器里，那你就错了
But if you think you could put a fish in there and it wouldn't get sucked into the mechanism,you'd be wrong.
可以借用洗手间吗？ 就在那里面
Can I use your bathroom?It's right through there.
要是一个星期前有人对我说
You know,I gotta tell you.If someone told me a week ago
我会在乔伊崔比亚尼家撒尿…
that I would be peeing in Joey Tribbiani's apartment...
人生真美好对吧？
Life's pretty great,isn't it?
希望你饿了，我们先吃生蚝
I hope you're hungry.We're starting with oysters.
你知道生蚝的作用吧？
You know what they say about oysters,don't you?
它有寄生虫？
They have parasites?
不是
No
有人说生蚝是一种春药
Some people say that oysters are an aphrodisiac.
什么人说的？ 就是人嘛，有人说的
-What people? -People.People say it.
过来
Come here.
生蚝是吧？
So,oysters,huh?
然后再吃一些中东的库司库司
Then we'll have a little Middle Eastern couscous.
我们可以用手拿着吃
Something we can eat...with our hands.
有意思，我们学到传染病时…
When we were studying communicable diseases..
不是
No,no. No.
这样才有感觉
It's sensual.
我都不知道，好 好
Didn't know. Okay.
讨厌
No
抱歉，医院找我
Sorry,it's the hospital.
菜都很棒，帮我留一点？
The food looks great. Save me some?
我可不敢保证
I can't promise anything.
我们是来真的对吧？
We're really gonna do this?
看样子是
Looks like it.
要是你觉得很怪 我们还是可以随时喊停…
If this is too weird for you,you can still back out anytime..
我来开 好
I got it!
苏珊
Susan
谢谢你的加入 我怎么可能错过
-Thank you so much for coming. -I wouldn't have missed it for the world.
我是罗斯
I'm Ross,by the way.
罗斯你好
Hello,Ross.
我喜欢你家的布置 谢谢你
-I love what you've done with this space. -Thank you so much.
好火辣呀
How hot is this?!
可惜在这里的是我不是罗杰
I'm sorry you're here with me instead of Roger.
就是啊
Yeah,me too.
我可以让你感到他的存在
Well,I could make it seem like he's here.
关于库司库司的小常识
"Here's some little-known facts about couscous:
第二个库司 是1979年才加的
They didn't add the second 'cous' until 1979."
别闹了，一点也不好笑
Stop it! That's not funny!
好 对不起
I'm sorry,okay? It's just...
今晚原本应该很重要的
tonight was supposed to be a big deal.
今晚要干嘛？ 你不会想知道
-What was tonight? -You don't want to know.
好吧
Okey
今晚要干嘛？
What was tonight?
今晚本来是我的初夜
Tonight was going to be my first time.
跟罗杰的第一次？
With Roger?
是你的第一次？我的天哪
Not just with Roger?Oh,my God.
别激动，只做过四次的先生
All right,relax,Mr. I've-Had-Sex-Four-Times!
是四个不同的女人 次数就多太多了
Four different women!I've had sex way more times.
几次？ 九次
-How many? -Nine.
我只是在等完美的对象
I'm just waiting for the perfect guy.
这样很好啊 你真的觉得罗杰是那个人？
Good for you. You really think that Roger's the perfect guy?
不是，但他也不算糟
No,but he's not a horrible guy.
我都那样自我介绍
That's what I tell girls about me.
钱德，我会死于处女之身
Chandler,I'm gonna die a virgin!
你不会，你很好很棒 你一定会如愿以偿
No,you are not. You are sweet and wonderful...and this is gonna happen for you.
是吗？什么时候？
Oh,really? When?
你想跟我做吗？ 好啊
Do you want to do it with me?Okay.
我是开玩笑的
I was kidding.
我也是
So was I.
乔伊，你真是个了不起的演员
You're such an amazing actor.
你怎么分辨雷莫瑞医生 跟乔伊崔比亚尼的转换？
How do you know where Dr. Drake Ramoray leaves off...and Joey Tribbiani begins?
雷莫瑞医生有现成的台词
Well,with Dr. Drake...they always tell me what to say.
乔伊就得自己编了
And with Joey,I pretty much have to make it up on my own.
你告诉我…
Tell me something,Joey.
我刚刚从沙发上摔下来 没错
-I just fell right off the couch there. -Yeah,you did.
坐好，我问你一件事
Here you go. Let me ask you a question.
有多久没有人称赞你美丽了？
When was the last time...someone told you just how beautiful you are?
我的手麻了
I can't feel my hands.
手给我
Come on. Come here.
我们不能这么做 没错
We can't do this.
吃生蚝？ 好
Oyster?
要是我们做了，我压力会很大
If we did do this,there'd be a lot of pressure on me.
因为你等了很久 我不想让你失望
Because you've waited a long time,and I wouldn't want to disappoint you.
但是我没得比较
But I have nothing to compare it to.
就算你很逊，我哪会知道？
Even if you were horrible,how would I know?
不错
I do like that.
我还比较累 我得跟另外四个女人比
It's harder for me. I have four women to compete with.
其实只有三个
Well,if it helps,there were only three.
所以只有今晚对吧？
So it'd just be for tonight,right?
没错，只是朋友在帮朋友的忙
Absolutely. It would just be one friend helping out another friend.
别说了，不行
Stop it. We're not doing this.
来做吧 不行…好吧
-Let's do it! -No!Okay!
你有特定的步骤吗？
Do you have any moves?
我有一些啦
I have some moves.
我没有
I have no moves.
你在干什么？
Okay,what you doing there?
对不起，真的太奇怪了 是啊，还是算了
-I'm sorry,this is just too weird. -Yeah,forget it.
要是我关灯呢？ 好
What if I turn out the lights?
钱德？ 怎样？
Chandler？  Ya？
那是沙发
That's the couch.
我知道
I know.
我的天哪
Oh,my God!
我知道
I know!
告诉你，我们一定要再来一次
I'll tell you something.We are gonna do that again!
没问题
Okey
早安
Morning.
对喔 没错
Oh,right.
天哪，居然让乔伊崔比亚尼 听到我吐
Oh,God.Oh,I can't believe Joey Tribbiani heard me throw up.
其实他也看到了一点 不会吧
He actually saw you a little bit too.
天哪，我们没有…没有…
Oh,God,we didn't...?
没有，看完就没兴致了
No No No，Not after seeing that.
我真是很糟糕
God,I'm just a horrible person.
为什么？ 因为我已经结婚了
-Wh..? Why? -Because I'm married.
没错，我是有夫之妇
That's right,I'm a married woman.
还跑到一个电视明星家搞外遇
I came to a TV star's apartment to have an affair.
别傻了
That's ridiculous.
我才不是明星
I'm not a "star."
只是一般的名演员
I'm just a regular famous actor.
而我是个很糟糕的人
And I'm a horrible,horrible person.
瑞秋，你别再自责了
Rachel,will you stop saying that?
你记不记得卡普丽丝临死前
Hey,look.Remember on the show when Capri was dying?
给了我… 石洞里的戒指，记得
-And she gave me.. -The ring from the cave.
天哪，你可以留着它？
Oh,my God! They let you keep that stuff?
当然，只要不被发现 想留什么都行
Sure. As long as they don't find out,you can keep whatever you want.
我要把它送给你
And I want you to have it.
不要… 要
No,I couldn't.
你每次看到它 就要想起你是个好人
Every time you look at it...I want you to remember that you are a good person.
你有机会外遇，而且还是跟我
Now,you had the chance to cheat...and with me.
但是你没有 这就是这枚戒指的意义
But you didn't. And that's what this ring stands for.
我以为它是代表 卡普丽丝对哥哥永不止息的爱
But I thought that ring stood for Capri's undying love for her brother.
你到底要不要？ 我要
Look,you want the ring or not?
你醒了 太好了
Hey,look at you! You're up!
我想去走一走
I thought I'd try to take a walk.
你们帮我倒杯水，我马上回来
Will you pour me some water? I'll be back soon.
你不是想打公共电话回公司吧
You're not gonna use the pay phone to call work,are you?
不是，我已经学到教训了
No. I've learned my lesson.
快点，动作快
Let's go! Come on! Move it!
鞋子，公事包 谢了，祝你的胆囊早日康复
Shoes,briefcase. Thanks,Lou. Good luck with the gallbladder.
乔伊，你…你玩过3P吗？
Hey,Joe...did you ever have a threesome?
罗斯，我觉得卡萝很漂亮
Look,Ross,I think Carol's great,
我也相信你很有魅力，但是…
and I'm sure you're very attractive,but
不是，我之所以问你是因为…
No. The reason I'm asking is that...
我昨晚玩了3P
I sort of had one last night.
你？ 对
You?
漂亮，过瘾吗？ 还…
All right. So? Was it amazing?It was...
好啦
okay.
只有还好？你的玩法对吗？
Just okay? Did you do it right?
你有没有在参加派对时觉得
Look,it's just,did you ever go to a party and think:
“少了我会有什么差别吗”？
"Would anyone really miss me if I weren't here?"
不过跟两个女人再难玩
But still,Ross...your worst day with two women,
也胜过其他日子，你懂吧？ 那当然
pretty much better than any other day.
只是我这个部分很快就结束了
It's just...my part seemed to be over pretty quickly...
然后我就一直等
and then there was a lot of waiting around.
你跟两个都有做到吧？
But you got to be with both of them.
没有
Not really.
我只有跟卡萝做
Just Carol.
另一个没有？ 没有，她一直把我踹开
-Not the other one? -No,she kept kicking me away.
那样很讨厌 就是啊
You don't want that.
至少你开了眼界
At least you got to see a lot of stuff.
是大大的开了眼界
Oh,I saw a lot of stuff.
你后来有点无聊？ 有一点
-You get a little bored? -A little.
我弄了点吃的
Made a snack.
你弄了什么？ 就是三明治
-What'd you have? -Just a sandwich.
火鸡肉，加一点芥末酱
Turkey. A little mustard.
好像不错 是很不错
-Sounds good. -It really was.
我昨晚跟一个女生过夜了
Let me tell you about this chick I scored with last night.
等等，就是你嘛
Wait a minute,that was you.
你看我，我是个贱人
Hey,check me out. I'm a slut!
晚上要不要找事情做？
So you want to do something tonight?
不行，罗杰医生又要来了
I can't. Dr. Roger's coming over again.
也对，因为你还在跟他交往
Oh,right.Because you're still seeing him,
他人很好，我记得有一次…
and he's a good guy.I remember a time....
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
好得很…你呢？
Yeah,totally.Totally. Are you?
很好，真的好神奇 上次罗杰来的时候我好紧张
Great. It's so amazing.Last time Dr. Roger came over,I was so nervous.
但是跟你做过之后，我变成
But after being with you,I'm like,
“医生可以看我了吗？”
"Can the doctor see me now?"
一定可以
I bet he can.
我没有预约，但是我需要体检
"l don't have an appointment,but I sure could use a physical."
你真的没事？
-You sure you're okay?
没事，别管我，我很好
-Don't worry about me,I'll be fine.
天哪，贝瑞
My God! Barry!
你说你周末都不在
You said you were going to be away all weekend!
没错，对不起，我回来早了 你们请继续
That's right! I'm sorry! I am early!Finish,please!
惊喜吧！看看谁回来了
Surprise! Look who's back!
菲比
Phoebe
通知警卫
Call security.
菲比，你不是被开除了吗？
Phoebe,didn't you get fired?
我可不这么认为
I don't think so.
菲比？ 杰克
Phoebe？ Jack
你来干什么？
-What are you doing here?
我好多了，回来上班
-All better. Back to work.
但这个研究部的小丑说我被开除了，他应该用功一点
This clown from research told me I was fired.He should do his research,huh?
你是被开除了
Well,you were fired.
没有
No
我跟帮你接电话的人说了
I told that guy who answered your phone.
我没收到留言，所以不算
I didn't get that message. So this doesn't count.
我先进办公室了
Anyway,I'll be in my office.
菲比，没有你的办公室
Phoebe,you don't have an office.
没关系，我在这里工作 这里很好，旁边有植物
I'll work right here.This is good. Next to this plant.
菲比…
Phoebe
你闯入我的办公室了
You're in my office.
我替这家公司赚了很多钱 而且是大钱
I've made a lot of cash for this company. I am talking big bucks!
披索、日圆、卢布 我才犯了一个小错…
Pesos! Yen! Rubles! You make one little mistake..
你损失了1千3百万元
You lost 13 million dollars.
原来一切都是为了钱
So now this is all about money?
我已经够…
You know,it's bad enough that...
别闹了吧
You have got to be kidding.
你还好吗？
-Are you all right?
我又发作了 什么？
-I'm having another heart attack.
我的心脏病又发作了 拨911
I'm having another heart attack!Call 911!
笨蛋
Dumb-ass!
菲比，你好吗？
Phoebe,how's it going?
我被开除，心脏病发作
They fired me,and I'm having a heart attack.
欢迎回来
Well,welcome back.
罗斯 瑞秋
Hi Ross！  Hi Rachel！
乔伊崔比亚尼在吗？ 不在
Is Joey Tribbiani here?  No
如果你见到他 请转告他我在找他
If you see him,please tell him I'm looking for him...
这次我不会吐了
and that this time I am not gonna throw up!
这永远是件好事
Well,that's always good news.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我？我很好 我很好，我好得不得了
Me? I'm great!I'm fine! I'm so good!
但是你知道谁不好？男人
But you know who's not great?Men!
你是男人对吧？ 对
You're a man,right,Ross?
坐下 好
Sit down.
我问你一件事
Let me ask you something.
婚誓对你们来说是个屁吗？
Do wedding vows mean squat to you people?
为什么我们一说要出门，砰！
Why is it that the second we tell you we are going out of town...
你们就跟邻居的 遛狗小妹上床？
bam,there you are in bed with the neighbor's dog-walker?
我们很抱歉
We're sorry.
我说真的，婚姻的神圣性呢？
No,seriously. Seriously. What has happened to the sanctity of marriage?
你昨晚不是跟乔伊在一起吗？
-Didn't you spend last night at Joey's?
你是侦探吗？
-What are you,a detective?
我不知道你和你丈夫怎么了…
I don't know what's going on with you and your husband...
希望那位遛狗妹已经成年
and what is hopefully an adult dog-walker.
但我要说男人并非都那样
Look,can I just say,not all men are like that.
有些男人愿意尽全力挽回婚姻
There are men who'll do anything to make their marriage work.
有些男人愿意退到一边
Men who will stand by and watch...
看老婆跟健身房刚认识的女人
as their wives engage in what can only be described as a "twosome"...
打得火热旁若无人
with some woman she barely knows from the gym!
这些男人是谁？
Who are these men?
就是我认识的一个人
Just men. A guy I know.
你可能要告诉他 听起来他的老婆是…同性恋
Well,you might want to tell him it sounds like his wife...is gay.
她才不是…
She is not...
她是同性恋
She's gay.
天哪
Oh,my God.
她好同性恋
She is so gay!
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
已婚者的吉日，对吧
Good day for married people,huh?
很遗撼你老公不忠
I'm sorry your husband cheated on you.
很遗撼你老婆是同性恋
I'm sorry your wife is gay.
看来女人也没那么好
I guess women aren't that great either.
去告诉我老婆啊
Try telling my wife that.
我可以进来吗？
Okay to come in?
进来，吃饭，随你便
Come in,eat,whatever you want.
罗杰医生又被叫走了
Dr. Roger got beeped again.
我知道，你猜是谁找他？
Yeah,I know. Guess who beeped him.
什么？ 我就是那个脾脏破裂患者
What？I'm the ruptured spleen.
你为什么要这样？
Why would you do that?
因为你不该和他在一起
Because you shouldn't be with him.
你应该和我在一起
You should be with me.
是吗？ 对
Really?
听你聊罗杰让我好痛苦
When you were talking about Roger,that was killing me.
昨晚的事不是说有就有的 至少对我来说不是
Things like last night,they don't just happen.At least not to me.
跟另外两个女人在一起时…
I mean,with the other two women...
到了早上 我巴不得赶快去找朋友
in the morning,I couldn't wait to go hang out with my friends.
但是跟你…
But with you...
我就是跟朋友在一起
I was,you know,already with a friend.
钱德
Chandler
你八成不想跟我交往 因为我太爱开玩笑
You probably don't want to go out with me.I make too many jokes,
也没认真谈过感情 又不是个“医生”
I've never been in a serious relationship...and I'm not technically a "doctor."
只有一个女人对不对？
There was just one woman,wasn't there?
真的有两个
No,there were two.
算上我？ 正是
-Including me? -Oh,yeah.
两次心脏病发才终于让你认清
It only takes two heart attacks To finally make you see
一次死不了 但第二次会让你解脱
One of them won't do it But the second will set you free
告诉你的恨意与愤怒 是该道别了
Tell all your hate and anger It's time to say goodbye
只要我的老板们一死 我就会这么做
And that is just what I will do Soon as those bastards I worked for Die